Seward, Ralph T. Additional Arbitration Files 5700
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Ralph T. Seward Additional Arbitration Files
1950-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seward, Ralph T.
5700
18 cubic feet
18 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists of arbitrations mostly to do with the UAW, Teamsters, Newspaper workers, and Airline workers.
3122638
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 01, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 27, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Arbitrator and mediator; member, National Mediation Service, National Defense Mediation Board; impartial umpire for cases involving the dairy, auto and steel industries, among others.
Ralph Seward (BA., Cornell University, 1927; MA., New York University, 1931; LLB., Columbia University, 1935) served as an attorney with the National Labor Relations Board (1936-1937) and was executive secretary (1937-1939) and general counsel (1939) of the New York State Labor Relations Board. He also served as chairman of the Board of Immigration Appeals, U.S. Department of Justice (1939-1941), as executive secretary, National Defense Mediation Board (1941-1942), and as associate public member of the U.S. National War Labor Board (1942) before going into private practice as an arbitrator and mediator. In addition to chairing two Emergency Boards of the National Mediation Service, Seward was impartial chairman for the metropolitan New York milk industry (1942-1944); impartial umpire for General Motors Corporation and the United Automobile Workers (1944-1947); chairman of the Board of Conciliation and Arbitration of United States Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America (1947-1949); impartial umpire for International Harvester Company and United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America (1949-1951); impartial umpire for Bethlehem Steel Corporation and the United Steelworkers of America (1952); and arbitrator and/or mediator in various other cases.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5069: U.S. Wage Stabilization Board 1952 United Steelworkers of America Case 5113: Ralph T. Seward Arbitration Transcripts and Exhibits 5328: Ralph T. Seward Papers
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Seward, Ralph T. (Ralph Theodore), 1907-
3122638
- Milwaukee Journal, et al. RTS Decision, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Milwaukee Journal, et al. Exhibits Nos. P-S-E 1 thru 22, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Milwaukee Journal, et al. Briefs: Union (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Milwaukee Journal, et al.: Exhibits -- PJE 1 thru PJE 22, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Milwaukee Journal, et al. - Exhibits - Board Exhibits Nos. 1 thru 3, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Milwaukee Journal, Et al. - Exhibits - Nos. P-S 1 thru P-S 8, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Milwaukee Journal, et al. - Exhibits - PJ-1 thru PJ-24, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Milwaukee Journal, et al. - Exhibits - Union No. 1 thru 38, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Milwaukee Journal, et al. Briefs - Publishers, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Milwaukee Journal, et al. Union's Dissenting (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Conemaught and Black Lick RR. Co. United Steelworkers 3176 Grievances Co., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Washington Post Company Washington Newspaper Guild AAA, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corp. Aluminum Workers Local 225, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bethlehem Steel - Pottstown Plant, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- United Airlines and Int. Assoc. of Machinists, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Graphics Arts Association Columbia Typographical Union No. 101 "Nugent Brown vs. Union Employers Div., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Graphic Arts Association Columbia Typo. Union No. 101, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Virginia Electric and Power Company, Award, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Pressman (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound 10 Photographs
- Printing an 8-Page Newspaper Straight 16-Page Newspaper Collect on the Goss Headliner, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Milwaukee Web Pressmen's Union, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Milwaukee Web Pressmen's Union, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Milwaukee Web Pressmen's Union, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Milwaukee Web Pressmen's Union, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Milwaukee Journal, et al. Charts - Extra (Blackboard), 1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- IHC - Milwaukee Works - Local 22631, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Kennecott Copper, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kennecott Copper Corporation United Steelworkers 4413 Grievances 51-62-22, 51-63-55, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- International Harvester-Balto. Motor Truck Int. Assoc. Mach. Lodge 199/ Branch Grievance F. Dickens, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- International Harvester-Emeryville UAAAIWA 76 Classification Dispute, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- International Harvester-Canton UAAAIWA 1145 Qualification of Employee Gaynell B. Nash, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- International Harvester - Indianapolis Works UAAAIWA 98 Case 1: Classification Dispute L-93 v L-94, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- International Harvester- Memphis Works UAAAIWA 988 Case No. 5, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- International Harvester- Memphis Works UAAAIWA 988 Case No. 6, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- International Harvester- Ft. Wayne UAAAIWA 57 Case No. 4 Military Furlough, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- International Harvester -Farmall Works UAAAIWA 1309 Classification Dispute P-135 v P-160, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- International Harvester - Farmall Works UAAAIWA 1309 Case No 8: Probationary Termination, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- International Harvester- West Pull- UAAAIWA 307 Classification Dispute P-84-A v B, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Aerospace Strike (Missile) Hearing (Los Angeles) July 30, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Chesapeake and Potomac Tel. Co. of Va. Communications workers of America, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Wilson and Co., Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen's Local No. 393, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Kansas City Star, The Kansas City Webb Pressmen Union No. 14 -Overtime Dispute-, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Kansas City Power and Light I.B.E.W. Local Union 1613 Holiday Pay Question, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Milk Industry- Local 680 Pension and Welfare Fund Union Trustees and Management Trustees, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Co. Niagara Falls Plant and Niagara Plant Employees Union Overtime Violation- Art. Section 6, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- American Airlines - Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Assoc. 550 Discharge Cases Nos. SS-16-68 -and- SS-17-68, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Western Airlines, Inc. - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (L.A.) RTS AD HOC, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Western Airlines, Inc. -Los Angeles, Fees and Expenses, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Western Airlines vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters Ad Hoc Transcripts, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Western Airlines vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters RTS Ad Hoc Union Exhibits, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Western Airlines - Company Exhibits Nos. 1-58, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- New England High Carbon Wire and United Steelworkers Incentive Arbitration Award, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- C and P Telephone Co. of Maryland Communications Workers of America RTS AD HOC., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- C and P Telephone Company Fees and Expenses: RTS (Ad Hoc) Hearing Date: March 8, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Communications Workers of America and South Central Bell Telephone Company. Mobile, Alabama., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- So. Central Bell Telephone Co. Fees and Expenses: RTS Mobile, Alabama, May 19-22, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- American Airlines, Inc. -RTS, AD HOC Stewardesses Local 550 Gr. SS-13-71, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- American Airlines, Inc. -RTS, AD-HOC Stewardesses Local No. 550, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- American Airlines, Inc. Fees and Expenses: RTS Hearing: March 3-4, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Airlines, Inc. - Miami, Fla. Air Line Dispatchers Assoc. Case No. 2-68, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Machinists and Aerospace Workers vs. United Assoc. of Journeymen and Apprentices of Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the U.S. 2nd Canada, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Machinists and Aerospace Workers vs. IBEW, Bremerton Washington Heard: January 7, 1970 a.m. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Southern Bell Telephone v. CWA Greensville, So. Carolina Hearings: February 26, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Post Office - Hearing: December 5, 1972 One Case (Box 7, Folder 2)
- U.S. Postal Service (RTS AD Hoc) National Association Letter Carriers Expense File: Hearings 12/5 and 8/72, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- National Football League W. Jones vs. St. Louis Cardinals, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- St. Louis Cardinals vs. Wendel Jones RTS (Ad Hoc) Fees and Expenses, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Titanium Metal Corp of America USWA, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Titanium Metal Corp. USWA, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Titanium Metal Corp. of America USWA, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Titanium Metals USWA, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Titanium Metals Corp. USWA, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Alleghany Ludlum - USWA, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Alleghany Ludlum Industries, Inc. United Steelworkers Correspondence Files, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Postal Service - National Agreement, Contracts, Amendments, etc., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Memphis Publishing Company - RTS Newspaper Pressmen, LU 24 Hearings (No. 2), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Memphis Newspaper Printing, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Memphis Hearings 12/17 - 18/75, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Memphis Notes Joint Exhibits, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Memphis Company Exhibits, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Memphis Union Exhibits, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Briefs Etc., 1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Memphis Publishing Company Memphis Newspaper Printing Pressman's Union No. 24, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Bermuda - Exhibits, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Duplicates, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Gould, Inc. - UAW AAA Case Hearing: Cleveland, Ohio March 22-23, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Gould Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Union 14, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Ralph T. Seward, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Ralph T. Seward, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Ralph T. Seward, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Bermuda, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Bermuda RTS Notes Etc., 1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Bermuda Arbitration Panel, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Board of Inquiry - Bermuda Industrial Union, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Wednesday, 31st March, 1976 Commencement (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Thursday April 1, 1976 Commencement (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Friday, 2nd April, 1976 Commencement (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Morning Session 9.4.76, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Morning Session 10.4.76, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Morning Session 13.4.76, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Morning Session 14.4.76, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Morning Session 15.4.76, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- 27th April 1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- 28th April, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- 29th April, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- 30th April 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- 1st May, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- 31st May 1976 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Bermuda Background (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Bermuda Working Papers, 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Bermuda Hotel Exhibits, 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Bermuda - Heb 15-26, 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Hotel Employees of Bermuda Exhibit 22, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Bermuda Board Exhibits, 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Wages Etc., 1976 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Bermuda Hotel Exhibits 30-69, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Bermuda Union Exhibits, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- U. 16, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Kansas City Area Transportation Authority and Amalgamated Transit Union AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Bound
- In the Matter of Arbitration between The Kansas City Area Transportation Authority and Local 1287, Amalgamated Transit Union, AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Kansas City Transit Authority Exhibits 161-265 Volume No. 2, 1960-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Area Transit Authority of Kansas City, Missouri -and- Local 1287, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Area transit Authority -and- Division 1387, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Area Transit Authority -and- Division 1287 Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Area Transit Authority -and- Division 1287, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Area Transit Authority -and- Division 1287 Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Area Transit Authority -and- Division 1287, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Area Transit Authority -and- Division 1287, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Area Transit Authority -and- Division 1287, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Area Transit Authority -and- Division 1287, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Joint Contracts/Agreements, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Kansas City Area Transit Authority -and- Division 1287, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Transit Union Exhibits Volume 2, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Transit Union Exhibits Volume. 1, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Kansas City Transit Authority Exhibits 1-160 Volume No. 1, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Kansas City Area Trans. Authority Amalgamated Transit Union, 1287, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Misc., 1976 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Misc. (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Station Service Manual, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Bermuda Hotel, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Bermuda Trip - April-May, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Hotel Employees of Bermuda Misc., 1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Hotel of Bermuda, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Washington Gas Company -and- OPEIU, Local 2 RTS ad HOC, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Washington Gas vs. Office Workers, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Timet-USWA, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Timet, Inc. Expense File Hearing: RTS, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- New England Telephone Expense File AAA Case 9/2/76, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- "Rule of 65" Arbtn. Panel Hearing Wash., D.C., 1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Coordinating Committee Steel Companies -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Rule of "65" Arbtn. Board Seward Garrett Aaron, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Washington Gas Co. Hearing: Jan. 18, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Wash. Gas Co. vs. Int. Gas Workers: Crew Mechanics Jobs, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Washington Gas-IUGW: Wash., D.C. Hearing: 11/9/76 RTS (Box 15, Folder 7)
- New York Telephone, N.Y.C. RTS Hearings: 12/15/77, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- So. Central Bell vs. CWA: Expenses Hearing: 11/14-16/77 New Orleans, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- New England Telephone: Expense File Hearing: 1/26-27/1978 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- New England Telephone U.S. IBEW Heard: 1/27/78 Decision: 8/28/78 Discharge of J. Needham Arbitration Board, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Southern Bell Telephone vs. CWA Hearing: 9/20/77: Greensboro, N.C., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- So. Bell Tel. vs. CWA: Greensboro, N.C. Expense File: Billed: 3/28/78, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- So. Bell Tel. vs. CWA Hearing: Jan. 29, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Pending, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Western Electric - IBEW, Hearing: 5/23-24/78 Phila, Pa., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Western Electric, Reading, Pa. Hearing:, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- So. Central Bell/ CWA: Birmingham, Alabama RTS, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Arbitration Seminar - AAA Monterey, Calif: 9/18-22/78, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- New York Telephone vs. CWA Ad Hoc Hearing: N.Y.C., 1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- The New York Telephone Company -and- Communications Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- So. Central Bell Enid Grice Discharge Transcripts, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- So. Central Bell Telephone Communications Workers Expense File Hearings 7/73, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- New York Telephone CWAL Case 1-75-93 Travel Allowance: R. Vanvoorhis, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Aerospace Special Panel - Memos, Legal Papers, RTS' Notes, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Aerospace Special Panel - Press Releases and News Releases 1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Aerospace, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Aerospace Special Panel - Press Releases and News Releases 1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Aerospace Panel - Expense File, GTR's and Travel Forms 1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Aerospace Special Panel - RTS Misc. File of ECM's, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Aerospace Panel - 1973 RTS: General File (Correspondence) Telephone Numbers (Box 18, Folder 10)
- 1973-1974 Aerospace Panel - File #2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Washington Publishers Assoc. International Printing and Graphic Union Hearing: 11/20/74, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- New York Telephone Co. and CWA, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)